(door closes)
(Amy:)It's not a big deal.
(Amy:)I run tests like this on
undergrads all the time.
(Amy:)If you fill out some
paperwork at the university,
I can get you $5.
I don't want $5.
(Penny:)I want my dignity.
(Amy:)So what are we talking,
like, ten bucks?
(Barry:)Thank you.
Thanks.
(Leonard:)Sorry again.
No problem.
A-Are you sure
you're not him?
(Raj:)Uh, you can tell us.
(Raj:)We're scientists,
not crazy fanboys.
(Nathan Fillion:)All right, fine.
(Nathan Fillion:)I'm him.
(Raj:)And you're eating
alone at a deli.
(Raj:)I don't buy it--
you're not him.
(chuckles)
(Nathan Fillion:)I just wanted
to eat my lunch in peace.
(Nathan Fillion:)But I really am him.
(Nathan Fillion:)And thank you very much
for being a fan.
(Nathan Fillion:)If you want, uh,
let's take a picture.
(Howard:)That would be great.
(Howard:)Great.
Yeah, thank you.
(Penny:)You bet.
(Raj:)Wait, hang on.